alive.com 2019-08-31

# Privacy Policy | Alive Magazine

We pledge to fully meet and, where possible, exceed internationally recognized standards of personal data privacy protection. In doing so, we will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.

We collect personally identifiable information such as identification and contact details of web visitors, information on their preferences in relation to the subject matter of the website, and payment-related information such as credit card details. Our purpose for collecting this information is to compile aggregate statistics on usage of alive.com. We also use personally identifiable information to manage magazine subscriptions.

We use cookies to gather demographic data and to track web traffic in various areas of the website. We do not disclose the gathered information to third parties. If your computer does not accept cookies, you may not have access to all parts of alive.com.

In the online store on our website, we collect information from visitors to the extent that it allows us to fulfill their order.

Web users have the opportunity to correct and update personally identifiable information by emailing us at [webmaster@alive.com](mailto:webmaster@alive.com).

We retain personally identifiable information indefinitely in order to provide you with our services. Users may request to retract personally identifiable information by emailing us at webmaster@alive.com.

If you would like to access your personal data or impersonal accumulated statistics, please send an email request to the webmaster at [webmaster@alive.com](mailto:webmaster@alive.com). We will handle your request promptly and provide this information to you within 40 days.

We do not disclose personally identifiable information to other parties except to facilitate an order made by the individual with a merchant hosted at the website. We do not sell personal data, including email addresses, to third parties. We reserve the right to disclose and print the names, addresses, photographs, and likenesses of contest winners and runners up for promotional and marketing purposes. We also disclose impersonally identifiable aggregate statistics relating to our web visitors to advertisers.

We use information collected from our visitors to market products or services to you. You can opt out of this kind of marketing by emailing us at [webmaster@alive.com](mailto:webmaster@alive.com). We comply with the opt-out requests we receive.

To ensure the security and confidentiality of personal data collected online, we use encryption for transmission of credit card details. Access to personal data is restricted to employees who need to use these details and who have been trained to observe confidentiality and handle such information appropriately.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

For any additional questions regarding our privacy policy and practices, please contact our webmaster at [webmaster@alive.com](mailto:webmaster@alive.com).
